Heezen-Tharp collection: Arctic Ocean
Geography and Map Division, Library of Congress
- Series II: Arctic Ocean
  - Group 21 - Arctic Ocean Published Maps, 17661007
    - 0030 Arctic Ocean Floor (Folder Barcode: 00275706796)
      a. Blue/Black plate print. b. Covers the Arctic Ocean, completed by the National Geographic society, Oct. 1971. Includes Heezen, Tharp, and Berann data.
    - 0031 Seismicity of Arctic and Adjoining Regions, 1960-63 (Folder Barcode: 00275706796)
      a. Paper. b. Twelve maps, prepared by A.F. Espinosa and J.A. Michael of the USGS, 1984.
    - 0032 The Bering Sea (Folder Barcode: 00275706796)
      a. Negative transparency. b. ˚ East to 160˚ North and 150˚ to 66˚ From 50 West. Russian map.
    - 0033 The Bering Sea and Gulf of Alaska (Folder Barcode: 00275706796)
      a. Negative transparency. b. ˚ to 75˚ East and 50˚ West to 130˚ From 155 North. Russian map.
  - Group 22 - Arctic Ocean Miscellaneous, 17761018
    - 0001 [Sketch for Arctic Ocean Basin] (Folder Barcode: 00275706802)
    - 0002 [Sketch of Arctic Ocean Basin] (Folder Barcode: 00275706802)
    - 0003 [Contour Map] (Folder Barcode: 00275706802)
      a. Paper. b. 53˚ to 60˚ North and 30˚ to 20 ˚ West.
  - Group 23 - Arctic Ocean Miscellaneous Boxed Data, 18458148
    2 boxes; estimated 100 items
    - Box 1 (Box Barcode: 00212681386)
    - Box 2 (Box Barcode: 00212681398)